<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Jen-Chieh's Blog</title><link>http://example.com/blog/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Jen-Chieh's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>jcs090218@gmail.com (Jen-Chieh Shen)</managingEditor><webMaster>jcs090218@gmail.com (Jen-Chieh Shen)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 21:00:00 +0005</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.com/blog/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Long Journey with Emacs</title><link>http://example.com/blog/long-journey-with-emacs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 21:00:00 +0005</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/long-journey-with-emacs/</guid><description><![CDATA[⚠️ The intention of this post is to remind myself why Emacs isn&rsquo;t worth my time anymore.
I&rsquo;ve been using Emacs since 2015. I have developed more than 150 elisp packages, and maintained over 200 packages (including my packages). It&rsquo;s been a long journey staying in the Emacs community, I think it&rsquo;s a good for me to slow myself down and step back a little and think what I&rsquo;ve accomplished through out these years.]]></description></item><item><title>Fastest ELPA</title><link>http://example.com/blog/fastest-elpa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/fastest-elpa/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s the fastest ELPA? Let&amp;rsquo;s define it first! The ELPA runs the fastest? No, that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense. The ELPA serves you the fastest? Maybe.
The definition for fastest ELPA in this article means it builds your packages the fastest! You might wonder why and how! Let me explain it to you!
Normal ELPA, like MELPA, builds packages from the recipes directory, so it takes O(n) to do so. The more packages one ELPA holds, take longer the time to get packages to update to the server.</description></item><item><title>Emacs Eask 101 - Build tool</title><link>http://example.com/blog/emacs-eask-101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:00 +0005</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/emacs-eask-101/</guid><description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;ve developed more than 50 elisp packages, and maintain 100 or more of them. Developing an elisp package isn&rsquo;t easy for a beginner, especially for those who want to publish their package to an ELPA. e.g., GNU Elpa, NonGNU Elpa, MELPA, etc.
That&rsquo;s why I use Eask to help me develop elisp packages. Therefore, in this article, I&rsquo;m going to teach people how to use this tool to help you build your own elisp packages!]]></description></item><item><title>First server migration</title><link>http://example.com/blog/first-server-migration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/first-server-migration/</guid><description>I have always been using AWS as my main web hosting choice. But I have come to the point that I reckon the price and services aren&amp;rsquo;t something that I need. Therefore, I have decided to switch to another web hosting company just for another taste.
The main reasons are listed below:
AWS charges you money when you click on their services without notifying the user. I dislike how it functions.</description></item><item><title>Game Jam - Aug 2022</title><link>http://example.com/blog/game-jam-aug-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/game-jam-aug-2022/</guid><description>Timeline is placed in summer time, middle of July 2022, one of my friend (@henrykuh) invited me to join the Game Jam that he is going to host in Aug 2022. In the meantime, he has also invited me to rejoin the community MatchWorkshop , and become the headmaster of the Game Programming deparetment. Therefore, this Game Jam is treated as an opportunity to collaborate with other headmaster from other department in this community.</description></item><item><title>Emacs Eask - Alternative to Emacs Cask</title><link>http://example.com/blog/emacs-eask/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/emacs-eask/</guid><description>🔰 Introduction The name Eask came from Emacs Cask ; if you already know what Cask is and what it does, please skip this and forward to the next section.
(NOTE: Cask and Eask are interchangeable in this section)
Eask is the dependency management tool for Emacs Lisp. It&amp;rsquo;s like npm to Node.js; but it isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly the same since Eask has fewer tools than npm, plus their ecosystems are slightly different.</description></item><item><title>First static site generator</title><link>http://example.com/blog/first-static-site-generator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/first-static-site-generator/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m recently hooked by the static site generator, hence I have decided to create one for myself. Why not? The huge reason is that I could host the site using the GitHub&amp;rsquo;s static site hosting services, but the one I have previously created in 2018 API-Reference-Template. is server base, which is not generator base.
The static site generator isn&amp;rsquo;t hard to create, the most valuable technology is the frontend and UI/UX.</description></item><item><title>Automate Personal License Activation in Unity CI</title><link>http://example.com/blog/automate-personal-license-activation-in-unity-ci/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/automate-personal-license-activation-in-unity-ci/</guid><description><![CDATA[<p>Following up the thread, <a href="https://forum.unity.com/threads/my-disappointing-experience-using-unity-in-a-ci-pipeline.737678/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">My disappointing experience using Unity in a CI pipeline</a>
is also the biggest obstacle for me as well. Personal license (free version) of
Unity will expire in a period of time depends on your region. The licensing system
from Unity is partially contradict to the CI/CD concept since it will force
the user to update their secret <code>UNITY_LICENSE</code> on their GitHub Actions. (Notice
this does not apply to Plus/Pro users because they use a different licensing system!)
😖</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Why I left USYD</title><link>http://example.com/blog/why-i-left-usyd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/why-i-left-usyd/</guid><description>WIP
WIP
💬 Past experience WIP
😨 Puzzled WIP
❗ Awakening WIP
💬 Future WIP</description></item><item><title>In a dilemma</title><link>http://example.com/blog/%E9%81%87%E5%88%B0%E5%9B%B0%E9%9B%A3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/%E9%81%87%E5%88%B0%E5%9B%B0%E9%9B%A3/</guid><description>This is a record, a message from me to one of my ex-firned.
The talked was, 2020-05-06
While you are in a dilemma, we humans are totally normal to be afraid of it. This may be a process; afraid makes us strong and a much more experienced people. Humans suppose to grow like that! So let it be! Once you are afraid of something, don&amp;rsquo;t give up on trying it; think about the issue, think as hard as you can, and try to resolve it!</description></item></channel></rss>