<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Editor - Category - Jen-Chieh's Blog</title><link>http://example.com/blog/categories/editor/</link><description>Editor - Category - Jen-Chieh's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>jcs090218@gmail.com (Jen-Chieh Shen)</managingEditor><webMaster>jcs090218@gmail.com (Jen-Chieh Shen)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.com/blog/categories/editor/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emacs Eask - Alternative to Emacs Cask</title><link>http://example.com/blog/emacs-eask/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/emacs-eask/</guid><description>🔰 Introduction The name Eask is obviousely came from Emacs Cask ; if you already know what is Cask and what it does, please skip this and forward to the next section.
(NOTE: Cask and Eask are interchangeable in this section)
Eask is the dependency management tool for Emacs Lisp. It&amp;rsquo;s like npm to Node.js; but it isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly the same since Eask&amp;rsquo;s has less tool than npm, plus their ecosystems are slightly different.</description></item><item><title>Emacs vs Vim</title><link>http://example.com/blog/emacs-vs-vim/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/emacs-vs-vim/</guid><description>Precisely that I am neither an Emacs nor Vim expert. I am just an amateur that knows about the two editors with just amount of knowledge. If you check out two of my Emacs and Vim repo, this could be the worst experience of all time. I hold onto an idea that the editors are just a tool. Unless there are issues that hamper or paster my workflow, I will avoid changing the configuration to my editor.</description></item><item><title>Best Editor Ever</title><link>http://example.com/blog/best-editor-ever/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Jen-Chieh Shen</author><guid>http://example.com/blog/best-editor-ever/</guid><description>First the foremost, this article is all subjective opinions by me, and there are all kind of text editor for any kind of programmer. I think some programmer have some kind of religion, so I am not going to tell anyone to use any particular text editor. I believed text editor is just tool to help programmer make a software and get their job done.
At my previous post ' Framework I have been working&amp;hellip; (Part 2) ' I mentioned I watched a few episodes of ' Handmade Hero &amp;rsquo;s series.</description></item></channel></rss>